A Guide to the Grove Family Papers, 1884-1932: SC 0292
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Grove Family Papers,
1884-1932
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Grove Family
SC 0292
6.93 cubic feet; 21 boxes
The Grove Family Papers, 1884-1932, consists of correspondence and ephemera from the Grove Family of Luray in Page County, Virginia.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection open to research. Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection. Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the James Madison University Special Collections Library to use this collection.
Acquisition Information
This collection was acquired at the Large Antiques and Firearms Estate auction held by Green Valley Auctions on January 16, 2018.
Bio/Historical Note
John William Grove was born December 16, 1844, in Luray, Page County, Virginia. As an adult, he served as a Corporal with the Confederate Army from 1863-1865 as part of the 35th Battalion of the Virginia Cavalry until being paroled from the army on May 8, 1865. He then married Eliza Jane Koontz (1850-1871) in 1869 and had two children: Ella Grove (1870-1932) and William Wallace Grove (1872-1874). After Eliza's death on October 19, 1871, John William Grove married Laura Ann Brumback (1851-1926), and had four children with her: Arthur Ashby Grove (1883 - 1940), Jessimine "Jessie" Lee Grove (1887 - 1966), Harold Elton Grove (1889 - 1970), and Julia Anita Grove (1892 - 1976). In the mid-1880s, John William Grove opened the Grove and Brothers store with his brother Charles H. Grove (1849 –1925) in Luray. John William Grove's sons Arthur and Harold took over the store after their father's death in August 1924.
Arthur, often addressed as A. A. Grove, was a member of the National Guard and veteran of World War I, having fought in France as part of the 116th Infantry, 29th Division. He was also an active member of the community, participating in the Luray Rotary Club, the Summers-Koontz Camp No. 490, Sons of Confederate Veterans, and others.
After receiving her bachelor's degree in music from Vassar College in 1910, Julia "Anita" Grove became a music teacher and spent several months almost every year traveling throughout the United States visiting relatives (e.g., cousins, extended family) and friends of the family or friends from her time at school.
Jessie Grove married William Pendleton Hershberger on January 28, 1919.
Scope and Content
The Grove Family Papers, 1884-1932, consist of 21 boxes, primarily comprising family correspondence. The bulk of the collection is made up of family correspondence and the rest is made up of ephemera collected by the family. The correspondence is mainly letters sent to the group or individual indicated by the series, with the bulk of the correspondence in this collection being letters sent to Arthur and Julia Grove. Most of the letters concern updates concerning other family members and the community. Much of the collection consists of holiday cards sent to all members of the Grove Family over the years.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in nine series, with the first eight series comprising family correspondence, arranged by recipient and chronologically. Series nine consists of ephemera accumulated by the family and is arranged alphabetically.
Series 1: Grove Family Correspondence, 1884-1932
Series 2: Arthur Ashby Grove Correspondence, 1892-1932
Series 3: Julia Anita Grove Correspondence, 1900-1932
Series 4: Jessie Grove Hershberger Correspondence, 1903-1932
Series 5: Harold Elton Grove Correspondence, 1920-1932
Series 6: Laura Brumback Grove Correspondence, 1886-1926
Series 7: John William Grove Correspondence, 1890-1924
Series 8: Charles H. Grove Correspondence, 1891-1930
Series 9: Ephemera, 1887-1932
Bibliography
"Corp John William Grove (1844-1924) - Find A Grave..." Find A Grave. Accessed June 11, 2019. https://www.findagrave.com/memorial/8423540/john-william-grove.
"Women's College Finals This Week." Times Dispatch (Richmond, VA), May 23, 1910. https://chroniclingamerica.loc.gov/lccn/sn85038615/1910-05-23/ed-1/seq-12/#date1=1900&index=1&date2=1930&searchType=advanced&language=&sequence=0&words=Anita+Grove&proxdistance=5&state=Virginia&rows=20&ortext=&proxtext=Anita+Grove&phrasetext=&andtext=&dateFilterType=yearRange&page=1
Index Terms
Subjects:
Luray (Va.) -- History -- 19th century; Luray (Va.) -- History -- 20th century; Page County (Va.) -- History; Page County (Va.) -- Genealogy; Page County (Va.) -- Social life and customs
Genre and Form Terms:
Letters (correspondence); Christmas cards; Printed Ephemera; Newspaper clippings; Photographs; Advertisements; Pamphlets
- Series 1: Grove Family Correspondence, 1884-1932
  Scope and Content
  Series 1: Grove Family Correspondence, 1884-1932, comprises correspondence that is either addressed to the Grove Family or correspondence for which there is no discernable individual family member that is the sender. Correspondence addressed to Elizabeth P. Barry, a friend of Julia and Jessie Grove, is included in this series. Most of the series is made up of correspondence either to the Grove and Brother Store from satisfied customers (thanking them for gifts, discounts, etc) or small holiday cards and wedding invitations from other members of the community.
  - Correspondence, 1884-1891 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1889-1931 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Grove Correspondence, 1895-1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1898-1900 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1901-1902 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1903-1904 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1910-1911 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Elizabeth P. Barry Correspondence, 1923-1930 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1924-1932 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Series 2: Arthur Ashby Grove Correspondence, 1892-1932
  Series 2: Arthur Ashby Grove Correspondence, 1892-1932, deals with the correspondence received by Arthur Ashby Grove between 1892 and 1932. Some interesting items in this series include letters sent by family while he was away training with the national guard in Virginia Beach and Richmond, Virginia and in Brownsville, Texas (dropping hints about potential brides in the area), some documents pertaining to military orders,inspections, some letters written in French, a letter from Anita telling Arthur about her first music pupil, letters from former comrades, and a letter written in 1922 from a Bulah Patterson that briefly asks Arthur's opinion on the Ku Klux Klan.
  - Correspondence, 1892-1898 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1898 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1901 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, February-June 1916 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, July 1916 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, August 1916 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, September 1916 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, October 1916 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, November 1916 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, December 1916 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, January 1917 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, February 1917 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1917 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1917 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, July 1917 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1919-1920 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1922 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, April-November 1922 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, December 1922 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1923 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, April-August 1923 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, December 1925 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, January-September 1926 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 3), December 1926 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 3), December 1926 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Folder 3 of 3), December 1926 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, January-November 1927 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 3), December 1927 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 3), December 1927 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (Folder 3 of 3), December 1927 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, April-November 1928 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, January-October 1930 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 3), December 1930 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 3), December 1930 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Folder 3 of 3), December 1930 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Series 3: Julia Anita Grove Correspondence, 1900-1932
  Series 3: Julia Anita Grove Correspondence, 1900-1932, deals with the correspondence received by Julia Anita Grove between the years 1900 and 1932. Most of the correspondence in this series come from family members and friends asking her about her travels and updating her on day-to-day activities in Luray. Examples of updates include a new "Ford shop" being built and their parents buying a new car, and an item of note is a souvenir folder from Rochester, New York that holds drawings of landmarks and facts about the city.
  - Correspondence, 1900-1920 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, February-October 1922 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), December 1922 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), December 1922 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January-May 1923 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, June-November 1923 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), December 1923 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), December 1923 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, January-May 1924 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, June-July 1924 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, August 1924 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, September-December 1924 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January-April 1925 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, May-November 1925 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 3), December 1925 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 3), December 1925 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Folder 3 of 3), December 1925 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, January 1926 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), February 1926 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), February 1926 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, March 1926 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, April-May 1926 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, June 1926 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, July 1926 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), August 1926 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), August 1926 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), September 1926 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), September 1926 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, October 1926 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, November 1926 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, December 1926 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, January 1927 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, March 1927 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, April 1927 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, May 1927 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, June 1927 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, July 1927 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, August 1927 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, September 1927 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, October 1927 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, November 1927 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 3), December 1927 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 3), December 1927 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Folder 3 of 3), December 1927 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, January 1928 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, February 1928 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, March 1928 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, April 1928 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, May 1928 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, June 1928 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, July 1928 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, August-September 1928 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, October 1928 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, November 1928 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, December 1928 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, January 1929 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, February 1929 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, March 1929 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, April 1929 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, May 1929 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, June 1929 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, August 1929 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, September 1929 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, October 1929 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, November 1929 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, December 1929 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, January 1930 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, February 1930 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, March 1930 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, April 1930 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1930 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, July 1930 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, August 1930 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, September 1930 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, November 1930 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), December 1930 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), December 1930 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, January 1931 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, February 1931 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, March 1931 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, April 1931 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, May 1931 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, June 1931 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, July 1931 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, August 1931 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, September-December 1931 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1932 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, April-November 1932 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 3), undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 3), undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Folder 3 of 3), undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Series 4: Jessie Grove Hershberger Correspondence, 1903-1932
  Series 4: Jessie Grove Hershberger Correspondence, 1903-1932, comprises correspondence received by Jessie Grove Hershberger between the years 1903 and 1932. Most of the correspondence is addressed to "Mrs. William P. Hershberger" or "Jessie Grove." Some interesting items include a small note where Jessie and Harold are invited to a spelling bee and instructed to "impersonate country school-children" in 1907 and a letter from a friend named Lottie in which she recounts interactions with patients in a hospital and asks Jessie for relationship advice (telling Jessie to "destroy the letter" after reading it).
  - Correspondence, 1903-1918 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Series 5: Harold Elton Grove Correspondence, 1920-1932
  Series 5: Harold Elton Grove Correspondence, 1920-1932, includes correspondence received by Harold Elton Grove between the years 1920-1932. Much of the correspondence comprises postcards from his relatives, updating him on the weather and sights. Some of the postcards come from Wyoming, New York, and Atlantic City.
  - Correspondence, 1917-1922 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, January-September 1930 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, December 1930 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Series 6: Laura Brumback Grove Correspondence, 1886-1926
  Series 6: Laura Brumback Grove Correspondence, 1886-1926, deals with correspondence received by Laura Brumback Grove between 1886 and 1926. Much of Laura's correspondence is from her children and step-children. Many of the envelopes are addressed not only to Laura but also to J.W (John William), but the greetings to these letters are always addressed to "Mama" or "Aunt Laura." Most of the correspondence during 1924 are letters of condolences and sympathies after John William Grove's death.
  - Correspondence, 1886-1903 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1915-1916 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1917-1918 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1919-1920 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 3), December 1925 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 3), December 1925 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 3 of 3), December 1925 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Series 7: John William Grove Correspondence, 1890-1924
  Series 7: John William Grove Correspondence, 1890-1924, deals with correspondence received by John William Grove between 1890 and 1924. Much of the correspondence comprises marriage and graduation invitations, holiday cards, and two letters written in 1924: one from his wife Laura and the other from his daughter Jessie.
  - Correspondence, 1890-1896 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1897-1901 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1902 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1903 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1909-1917 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1919-1920 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1924-1925, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Series 8: Charles H. Grove Correspondence, 1891-1930
  Series 8: Charles H. Grove Correspondence, 1891-1930, deals with correspondence received by Charles H. Grove between 1891 and 1930. As with his brother John, Charles's correspondence includes marriage announcements and graduation invitations, some letters from hotels asking for his business, and a couple of postcards from Anita telling him about her travels.
  - Correspondence, 1891-1899 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1900-1902 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1909-1930 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Series 9: Ephemera, 1887-1932
  Series 9: Ephemera, 1887-1932, includes myriad ephemeral materials that were accumulated the Grove Family. The series is arranged alphabetically. Some items of note within this series include military ephemera (containing some transfer orders and programs to numerous military events); music education ephemera (which include sheet music and small booklets pertaining to the popular songs of the time); some photos of a storefront and two unidentified individuals; and travel brochures, maps, and promotional materials of Virginia and other locations.
  - Banquet Menus, 1903-1907 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Book Catalogs/Libraries, 1925-1932, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Calendars/Notepads, 1917-1929 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Church Pamphlets, 1916-1925 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations (Folder 1 of 2), 1887-1930 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations (Folder 2 of 2), 1891-1932 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Educational Materials, 1890-1930 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Financial and Business Files, 1918-1929 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Grove and Brother Store Ephemera, 1905-1932 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Handwritten Notes, 1912-1925 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Life Insurance Ephemera, 1920-1928 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Military Ephemera (Folder 1 of 2), 1906-1923 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Military Ephemera, 1919-1929 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Ephemera, 1861-1923 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Music Ephemera (Folder 1 of 2), 1919-1929 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Music Ephemera, 1920-1933 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers, 1861-1929 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Page Valley National Bank Ephemera, 1904-1922, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, 1913-1929 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Poetry, 1906, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Postcards and Tags, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Materials and Advertisements (Folder 1 of 6), 1890-1930, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Promotional Materials and Advertisements (Folder 2 of 6), 1901-1929, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Promotional Materials and Advertisements (Folder 3 of 6), 1904-1929, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Materials and Advertisements (Folder 4 of 6), 1906-1920, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Materials and Advertisements (Folder 5 of 6), 1925, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Materials and Advertisements (Folder 6 of 6), 1926, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Rotary International Event Programs, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Sewing Patterns, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Travel Maps, 1910-1928 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Travel Ephemera (Folder 1 of 2), 1922-1930 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Travel Ephemera, 1929, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Promotional Advertisements, 1916-1924 (Box 21, Folder 10)